Futurama is brought to you by
Thompson's Teeth
The only teeth strong enough
to eat other teeth.
Good news, everyone.
Today marks our dear friend Dr. Zoidberg's
10th year with Planet Express.
Huzzahs are in order!
- Huzzah.
Hooray for me! Hooray for Zoidberg!
I will now read the mandatory speech.
"Dear employee,
"has it really been five, 10 or 15 years?
"If not, please disregard this
and get back to work."
Distribute token of appreciation
and applaud.
Look! Coupons!
I can get two oil changes
for the price of one!
Now if I could only afford the one.
And the car. Ah, the years.
So many memories.
So many strange fluids gushing
out of patients' bodies.
Yes, yes. Now here's
your pension statement.
It's empty because you haven't
paid into it, you dumb stinkbug!
You kept track of it all these years.
Oh, no! I'm boned!
I haven't paid into the pension, either.
What'll I do when I retire?
I thought you were retired.
Hey, I don't see you
planning for your old age.
I got plans.
I'm gonna turn my on/off switch to off.
Well, I'm gonna take action.
It's time to check on my retirement fund.
Damn. Still only $100.
A penny saved is a penny earned.
Also, could you get some
athlete's foot cream for my face?
He's right.
I've got to start investing wisely.
Well, down to my last lottery ticket.
Cherry.
Cherry!
Mule. Crud!
So, you got six bucks left to retire on.
I recommend Tender Vittles.
You're opening
a retirement account for $6?
I'm sure a wealthy mule farmer
like yourself
is aware that we charge a $10 monthly fee.
You gotta spend money to make money.
Here you are, sir.
Your account is now overdrawn by $4.
Jeez. I've seen lines move faster
in the sperm bank.
That's for... Roberto, is that you?
Bender! Hey, man!
You old lunatic! How ya been?
Oh, not bad. Not bad.
Everybody on the floor! This is a stickup!
Yeah, I'm doin' okay, too.
I'm takin' a Chinese cooking class
at the Learning Annex.
Cool. Can you give me a hand here?
Sure thing, pal.
Hey, you! Red!
Quit waterin' that plant and get the door!
- Well, nice talkin' to ya.
- Same here. You guys are all right.
Here's somethin' for your trouble.
Hey, thanks, buddy!
Freeze, punks! You're under arrest!
Shoot 'em in the back!
Quick, while they're not looking!
Court is in session.
The Honorable Judge Whitey presiding.
The charge is bank robbery.
Now, my caddy's chauffeur informs me
that a bank is a place where people
put money that isn't properly invested.
Therefore, robbing a bank is tantamount
to that most heinous of crimes,
theft of money.
As the surveillance camera for that bank
what all the judge was a-jawin' about,
could y'all tell us what you done seen
the day of the crime?
Well, let's see.
My memory's a little fuzzy,
but it went exactly like this.
Your Honor, I move that I be disbarred
for introducin' this evidence
against my own clients.
Mr. Fry, do you recognize
the robot a-huggin' on you
in this here hologram?
I sure do. That's the real robber.
And I'll never forget
his name as long as I live.
And that name is...
Fry, just give a name!
You don't want to look stupid on Court TV!
You're right. You're right. It was...
Yes? What?
You say if I testify I'll be killed?
Oh. It's for you.
And the other hamburger
will also be made of your lungs.
So long, pal.
I refuse to testify on the grounds
that my organs will be chopped up
into a patty.
Ah! The 67th Amendment.
I may be a simple country hyper-chicken,
but I know when we're finger-licked.
What do you say we plead insanity?
A few months in an insane asylum?
I could do that standin' on my head.
If you start now, it might help our case.
Counselor, what evidence do you offer
to support this new plea of insanity?
Well, for one,
they done hired me to represent them.
Insanity plea is accepted.
Mr. Bender,
I hereby commit you to the asylum
for criminally insane robots
until such time as you are deemed cured.
Yahoo!
The system fails again!
And Mr. Fry,
I sentence you to the home
for criminally insane humans.
Your Honor, that facility has been full
ever since you ruled
that being poor is a mental illness.
Order! Order!
The only poor people I want to hear about
are the people who tend
to my pores at the spa.
Just send them both
to the robot loony bin and let's go.
Ow! My head! Ow! My feet!
- Keep your chin up.
- Ow! My chin!
I don't belong here, Bender.
This is an asylum for insane robots.
Well, you meet half the qualifications.
Oh, good! A physical!
Once they examine
my fragile, naked, pink body,
they'll see I'm not a...
Whee!
Ooh! Ah!
What the...
I find that offensive!
Greetings. I am Dr. Perceptron.
Let me give you something
to help you relax.
Look, there's been a terrible mistake.
I'm a human being. See?
I'm all squishy and flabby.
Also, I complain a lot.
Yes, you do. You need to relax more.
Terrific.
Now consider the following.
You were admitted to this robot asylum.
Therefore, you must be a robot.
Diagnosis complete.
I do other human stuff! I age. See?
I'm Nurse Ratchet.
Please come with me, won't you?
We'll meet your roommate next, shall we?
His name is Malfunctioning Eddie.
The car dealer?
Wow. I guess his prices
really were insane.
He's very excitable.
So don't say anything to surprise him.
- Pleased to meet you.
- Actually, we've met once before.
What?
I'm a pretty girl. I'm a pretty girl.
I'm a pretty girl.
Whoa! Someone had a busy day.
My roommate exploded.
You gotta help me, Bender.
How can I prove I'm human?
You could drop dead. That'd show 'em.
I don't wanna!
Hey, man. I believe you're a human.
- You do?
- Sure.
They don't believe I'm a human, either.
Name's Unit 2013.
Come on. Let me introduce you around.
Fry, meet Norm. How's it goin', pal?
Still pickin' up transmissions
from the CIA on your teeth?
They just won't stop!
The CIA Cafeteria menu
for the week of May 15 is as follows.
Monday, shepherd's pie.
Cuckoo.
Let me guess. He thinks he's Lincoln?
Well, he's supposed to. The problem is,
he's got multiple personalities,
all of 'em Lincoln.
I was born in 200 log cabins.
And this here is Frankie.
He's convinced he's a lunchroom worker.
So they put him to work in the lunchroom.
How is workin' the lunchroom, Frankie?
- It's all right.
- Poor Frankie.
Change places!
Bender, I can't take much more of this.
I want outta here!
Are you crazy? This place is great.
Electroshock whenever you want it.
Two Lincolns for every Napoleon.
Ah!
Sweet light crude.
But I'm not a robot like you!
I don't like having discs crammed into me.
Unless they're Oreos.
And then only in the mouth.
Don't you understand? I'm gonna die here.
Ah, quit your bellyachin'
and take it like a robot.
Change places!
The doctor says you are making
great strides with your exploding problem.
Well, the way I see it...
You gotta get me outta here.
I would have starved to death
if not for that sick
vending machine robot.
Give me! Give me!
Poor Fry.
He's got the munchies for freedom.
We're all trying to help you.
We've petitioned the governor.
But he doesn't want to appear soft
on people who've been falsely imprisoned.
At least I have friends on the outside.
Bender's been no help at all.
Je suis Napoleon!
Now, seriously, I'm not.
Bender, you should be more
ashamed of yourself than usual.
Lighten up, honey.
I'm just tryin' to get through
a difficult time using humor.
Visiting hours are over.
Time for our medication discs.
Help me! For God's sake, help me!
Oh, don't worry, Fry.
I, too, once spent a nightmarish time
in a robot asylum.
But now, it's nearly over. So long.
Thirty days hath September, April, June.
All the rest have peanut butter.
Now what?
Oh, God! What? What? What is it now?
You are being released.
Finally! Sweet justice!
Sweet, juicy justice!
Not you. Him.
Me? What a surprise!
Look! I barely exploded at all.
We can control that with medication.
Fry? Are we ready
to meet our new roommate?
Hi, Red!
Roberto? What are you doing here?
I got busted robbin' that bank again.
Why would you hold up the same bank twice?
That first time was just
to case the joint and rob it a little.
What's the matter? You scared?
Noticeably? I'll say.
Now, stand back.
I gotta practice my stabbin'.
No! Please! Help!
Stop it! Police!
Hey, keep it down in there!
I'm tunin' my banjo!
Geez, Red. Quit cowerin'.
You call yourself a robot?
I'm not a robot! I'm not a robot!
In answer to your question, Hermes,
yes, your friend is cured.
You'll notice he no longer
suffers delusions of humanity.
Affirmative. I feel nothing. I am a robot.
Beep, beep, beep, beep, beep...
You've made a terrible mistake.
He's a human being, not a machine!
Oh, Fry!
Beep, beep, beep, beep, beep...
Gonna sing a little tale
About a battle called Waterloo
Bonjour, y'all!
Listen to me, Fry.
Just because you think you're a robot
doesn't make you a robot.
After all, I think I'm a doctor,
but that doesn't make me a doctor.
These fancy clothes do.
Negative. I must be a robot.
Why else would human women
refuse to date me?
Oh. Lots of reasons.
Bio-units, terminate noise exchange.
It is time for you to ingest
sandwiches from my compartment.
Here we go. Just a minute.
And down the stretch,
it's Daddy's Little Grandpa,
followed by Perennial Loser
and bringing up the rear, it's Lasty!
- Come on, Lasty!
- Hey, Bender.
Roberto! Ooh! What a surprise
to see you in here!
Especially 'cause
I didn't squeal on ya, remember?
Remember all that squealin' I didn't do?
Remember? Do ya?
Yeah. Yeah. Now lie down and play dead.
- And don't ham it up.
- Sure. Anything for you, buddy.
Wait here, Bender.
I need to get a disguise.
Uh, what's with the getup?
I'm in disguise
'cause I'm thinkin' of escapin'.
You in? Or do I gotta kill ya
so ya don't squeal?
I'm in! I'm in!
So, when were you plannin' the breakout?
I'm thinkin' maybe a few seconds ago.
Quick! Let's keep escaping!
Times two, carry the one.
You sad, worthless human.
Sacred hog of Prague!
That was my anniversary gift to Labarbara.
Fear not, for I shall assist ye.
Robots don't say "ye."
Relax, mammal.
My robotic software
shall meet your calculatory needs.
What is the meaning of this symbol?
That's a plus sign, you pointy-head loony!
Quit thinkin' you're a robot!
I'll show ye.
Stand back! I'm a toolbot.
You're not a toolbot.
You're not a food-motron.
You're not a robot of any kind.
Yes, I am.
I simply haven't discovered
my primary function yet.
Okay. This has got to stop.
I'm going to remind Fry of his humanity
the way only a woman can.
You're going to do his laundry?
Fry, this is for you.
- Beep.
- Oh, for God's sake!
By a scallop's forelocks.
What's with all the beer, Fry?
Alcohol fuels my power cells.
And as a mighty robot, I...
Beep.
Thanks for helpin' me escape, Bender.
It was nothin'.
It was not nothin'! I want to repay you.
Let me get you somethin' in here.
Hands up! This is a stickup again!
Wow. Hitting the same place three times?
I admire your style, Roberto.
Give me the remainin' dough
and all the calendars.
And that pen!
Try to tear it so most of the beads
are on my end.
Police! You're busted!
And don't try anything.
This glass here is laser-proof.
Fire lasers!
Duck, lasers!
Come on! I got a place
where I like to hide after crimes.
Aw! He looks like a little
insane drunken angel.
Hey, everybody. Meet my good pal, Roberto.
- Hey, mon.
- Nice to meet you...
- Come out with your hands up!
- Hostages!
Back off! I got hostages!
Hooray! I'm helping.
Do you have any better hostages?
To show them who's crazy,
I'll execute some of you.
- How about you?
- Ouch!
That's going to bleed when my heart beats.
Wait! Take me first!
Yes! Take her first!
Shut up!
Stop tellin' me how to do this!
The fear.
I'm thinkin' of a number
between one and 10.
Guess it, and you die first. Go!
Um... Okay.
Fifty-six-ish?
Fifty-six? Fifty-six?
Oh, man! Now that's all I can think about!
I'm gonna kill you, you no-good 56-ing...
Don't kill me yet!
I'm startin' to come down
with Stockholm Syndrome, handsome.
Halt, fellow robot!
Hey, Red!
You're just in time
to join the hostage situation.
Which side do you want to be on?
The side that kicks
your twisted metal ass.
Fry! Stay back! He's too powerful!
Negative, bossy meat creature.
I know now what my primary function is.
I am a battle-droid,
sworn to protect the weak
from crazy robots.
I'm not crazy! Don't call me crazy!
I'm just not user-friendly.
Fry, don't be a hero!
It's not covered by the health plan!
Let's see how much
of a robot you really are...
No knife can penetrate
my skin-tanium armor.
Help! Help! He is a battle-droid!
Somebody help me!
Mommy!
I'm sorry I spilled
the transmission fluid, Mommy.
No, no! Don't weld me to the wall, Mommy!
We're willing to listen to your demands.
Hey, baby.
Wash that off before you put it back.
- Hooray!
- Bravo!
You did it, Fry.
Congratulations, buddy.
You're a credit to my race.
It was nothing. I... Ah!
Blood? Robots don't have blood.
- I must be a...
- A squid?
A human! Oh, my God!
- I'm a human!
- Also good.
Thanks for saving us, Fry.
I'm gonna continue
never washing this cheek again.
Buddy, you may be wrapped in greasy skin,
but inside,
you've got the heart of a robot.
Aw! Thanks, Bender.
Just like inside me,
I've got the heart of a human.
What?